<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="mohon_tunggu_sebentar">Please Wait</string>
    <string name="mau_eksplorasi_apa_hari_ini">What are you going to explore today?</string>
    <string name="pilihan_layanan">Services</string>
    <string name="lihat_semua">View All ></string>
    <string name="deteksi_air">Detect Water</string>
    <string name="deteksi_udara">Detect Air</string>
    <string name="deteksi_tanah">Detect Soil</string>
    <string name="tentang_envy">About Envy</string>
    <string name="app_desc">Envy (Environments Quality) is an application that allows users to detect and measure the quality of water, air, and soil based on predefined parameters. Envy provides results reports on environmental quality based on predetermined parameters so as to provide information that allows users to determine environmental quality in order to be able to take the next appropriate steps. This application helps users become agents of change who care about the environment.</string>
    <string name="dalam_pengembangan">Under Development :)</string>
    <string name="bahasa">Language</string>
    <string name="mode_malam">Night Mode</string>
    <string name="apa_sih_ide_dibalik_envy">Idea behind Envy</string>
    <string name="app_idea">A clean and healthy environment will improve the quality of life of the people living in it, broadly it is very important for humans to have a good quality environment for health in order to be able to live their daily life to the fullest.\n\nWater Quality Index (WQI) /Water Quality Index), Air Quality Index (AQI/Water Quality Index), and Soil Quality Index (SQI/Water Quality Index) are important measurement tools for determining environmental quality by reflecting the influence of various environmental quality parameters considered and used in calculating the water quality index, air quality index and soil quality index.\n\nWe had the idea to use the water quality index (WQI), Air Quality Index (AQI) and Soil Quality Index (SQI) datasets as inspiration to apply machine learning using a squential model with the help of the tensorflow library. The goal is to distinguish between the quality of a safe and proper environment for humans.</string>
    <string name="bagaimana_cara_deteksi">How to detect?</string>
    <string name="how_detect_water">1. Enter the values of all available element categories according to the conditions of the place to be detected.\n2. Press the Detect button.\n3. Voila, the predicted results will appear.</string>
    <string name="keterangan">Description</string>
    <string name="detect_water_how_desc">1. Fecal Coliform (FC) is a type of bacteria that is usually found in animal and human feces. Its presence in water indicates faecal contamination, which can be an indicator of contamination by pathogenic organisms.\n2. Oxygen (O2) is a gas that is essential to support life in water. The presence of sufficient oxygen in water is essential for the existence of aquatic organisms such as fish and other living things.\n3. Water PH (pH) is a measure of the level of acidity or alkalinity of water. The pH scale ranges from 0 to 14, where a value of 7 indicates neutral acidity, a number less than 7 indicates acidity, and a value greater than 7 indicates alkaline.\n4. Total Suspended Sediment (TSS) are solid particles contained in water and can be seen visually as turbidity or water turbidity. TSS often consists of sand, silt, soil and other organic matter, and can affect water quality and aquatic organisms.\n5. Temperature (Temp) is the temperature of the water. Water temperature can affect the survival and activity of aquatic organisms. Sharp temperature fluctuations or temperatures that do not correspond to natural conditions can negatively affect aquatic life.\n6. Nitrogen (N) is a chemical element that is important in the nutrient cycle. In water, nitrogen can exist in many forms, including ammonia, nitrate, and nitrite. The presence of nitrogen in the right amount is important for the growth and survival of aquatic organisms.\n7. Phosphorus (P) is a chemical element that is also important in the nutrient cycle. In water, phosphorus can exist in the form of phosphate. Phosphorus is an essential nutrient for the growth of plants and aquatic organisms. However, excess phosphorus in water can lead to ecological problems such as eutrophication and algal overgrowth.\n8. Turbidity (Turb) is a measure of the turbidity or turbidity of water due to the presence of suspended solids in it. Water turbidity can be affected by organic matter, sediment, sewage, or other pollutants. The level of water turbidity can affect water quality and affect aquatic life.</string>
    <string name="deteksi_disini">Detect Here</string>
    <string name="deteksi">Detect</string>
    <string name="hasil">Result</string>
    <string name="sistem_kami_memprediksi_bahwa_kualitas_air_di_tempat_kamu">Our system predicts that the water quality in your place is %s</string>
    <string name="detect_soil_desc">1. Nitrogen (N) is a chemical element that is an important part of proteins and other organic molecules. Nitrogen is needed by plants and other living things for growth and development. In aquatic ecosystems, nitrogen can exist in various forms such as ammonia, nitrate, and nitrite.\n2. Phosphorus (P) is a chemical element that is also important in the growth and development of organisms. Phosphorus is a major component in DNA, RNA, and adenosine triphosphate (ATP). Phosphorus is also an important nutrient in aquatic ecosystems, but excess phosphorus can cause ecological problems such as eutrophication and algal overgrowth.\n3. Potassium (K) is a chemical element needed by plants and other organisms as a nutrient. Potassium plays an important role in the regulation of osmotic pressure in plant cells, root development, and enzyme function. Potassium is also one of the macro elements needed in sufficient quantities by plants for optimal growth. Soil PH (pH) is a measure of the level of acidity or alkalinity of the soil. The soil pH scale ranges from 0 to 14, with a value of 7 indicating neutral acidity, a value less than 7 indicating acidity, and a value greater than 7 indicating alkaline. Soil pH affects the availability of nutrients for plants as well as the activity of microorganisms in the soil.</string>
    <string name="detect_air_desc">1. Particulates (PM2.5) are solid particles less than 2.5 micrometers in size in the air. These particulates can come from various sources such as burning fossil fuels, industry, motorized vehicles, development activities, and natural processes such as dust and pollen.\n2. Carbon Monoxide (CO) is a colorless and odorless gas that is formed from incomplete combustion of fossil fuels. CO can be a toxic gas that can bind to hemoglobin in human blood, inhibit oxygen transport, and has the potential to cause poisoning or death.\n3. Ozone (O3) is a form of oxygen consisting of three oxygen atoms. Ozone can be formed naturally in the upper atmosphere by the interaction of sunlight with pollutants such as nitrogen dioxide (NO2). Ozone can protect the ozone layer in the earth\'s atmosphere, but if it is present in high concentrations on the earth\'s surface, it can become an air pollutant that is harmful to humans and other organisms.\n4. Nitrogen Dioxide (NO2) is a brown gas formed from the reaction of nitrogen oxides (NO) with oxygen in the air. NO2 is an air pollutant produced by human activities such as burning fossil fuels. Long-term exposure to NO2 can cause health problems such as irritation of the respiratory tract, increased risk of respiratory infections and other respiratory problems.</string>
    <string name="ph_tanah_ph">Soil pH</string>
    <string name="sistem_kami_memprediksi_bahwa_kualitas_tanah_di_tempat_kamu">Our system predicts that the quality of the soil in your area is %s</string>
    <string name="sistem_kami_memprediksi_bahwa_kualitas_udara_di_tempat_kamu">Our system predicts that the air quality in your place is %s</string>
</resources>